NumPy has a module for random sampling,
NumPy 有一个随机样本模块
that makes it really easy for us to simulate random events like coin flips and Python.
我们可以很方便地模拟掷硬币和 Python 等随机事件
We're going to start with a simple example,
我们先举一个简单的例子
simulating a single coin flip.
模拟一次掷硬币
For this, we'll use a function called randint.
我们将使用一个称为 randint (随机整数) 的函数
This generates however many random integers,
但是 这会在我们指定的内含性下限与排他性上限之间
we specify between a lower bound inclusive and upper bound exclusive.
生成多个随机整数
We can use these integers to represent the outcomes of our events,
我们可以用这些整数代表事件的结果
like coin flips. Let's try this out.
例如掷硬币 我们试一下
We call randint from NumPy's random sampling module like this.
从 NumPy 的随机抽样模块中调用随机整数
Let's use zero to represent heads and one to represent tails.
用零代表正面 一代表背面
Let's make this function randomly produce zero or one.
让这个函数随机生成零或者一
The lower bound would be zero and the highest would be two, because it's exclusive.
下限将为零 上限将为二 因为它是排他性的
Since the lower bound is zero,
由于下限是零
this is actually the default.
这实际是默认值
We don't need to include it.
不需要包括它
If we run the cell again and again,
如果反复运行这个单元格
we'll keep getting a random outcome of zero or one or,
会不断获得零或者一的随机结果 或者
we can specify a size to just give us more events.
我们可以指定一个大小 以便获得更多事件
Cool. Now, we have the results of 10,000 random coin flips.
很好 现在 我们有一万次随机掷硬币的结果
The average of these outcomes produced here should be very close to 0.5,
这里生成的这些结果的平均值应该非常接近 0. 5
since right now there's an equal probability of getting a zero or a one.
因为现在获得零和一的概率是相等的
But what if we want to flip a biased coin,
但是如果我们想用偏性掷币法
that had a higher probability of landing on heads.
正面朝上的概率较大
There's actually another function for this called random.choice.
它实际上有另一个函数 叫做 random.choice (随机选择)
This function works a little differently.
这个函数的原理稍微不同
It randomly chooses a number of values from an array that you provide and you
它从你提供的一个阵列中随机选择多个值
can also give it a set of probabilities for each value in that array.
你也可以对阵列中的每个值赋予一组概率
Let's call random.choice and give it the array of the possible outcomes zero and one.
我们调用 random.choice 给它提供可能结果 （零和一）的阵列
If we don't specify probabilities,
如果不指定概率
it gives us each value and an equal probability by default.
它会给出每个值 并默认给出相等的概率
We can run this similar to the above example in this way.
我们可以用和上述示例相似的方式运行它
So the average is very close to 0.5 Again.
所以 平均值也非常接近 0.5
To make this a biased coin,
要用偏性掷币法
we can specify the parameter p with an array of probabilities.
我们可以用概率阵列指定参数 p
Say 0.8 for heads and 0-2 for tails.
假设正面是 0.8 背面是 0.2
Now, you can see that the mean is close to 0.2 which makes
现在 你可以看到均值接近 0.2
sense because the zero or heads should be chosen 80% of the time.
因为在 80% 的时间里选择的是零 (也就是正面)
You probably noticed that the mean values we get from
你可能注意到 我们从这些结果中获得的均值
these outcomes don't always reflect the true probabilities perfectly.
并不能始终准确反映实际概率
However, they do tend to reflect the true probability
但是 随着掷硬币次数的增加
more closely as we increase the number of flips.
它们能更接近地反映实际概率
You'll learn more about this later.
后续我们将进行更详细的讲解